<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <atom:link href="http://blog.locki.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <link>http://blog.locki.io/</link>
    <description></description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2017 00:13:31 +0900</pubDate>
    
      <item>
        <title>Screwdriver.cd released with bilingual documentation by Locki</title>
        <link>http://blog.locki.io/posts/screwdriver.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.locki.io/posts/screwdriver.html</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Yahoo’s open-source project &lt;a href=&quot;http://screwdriver.cd/&quot;&gt;Screwdriver&lt;/a&gt;, a Continuous Delivery Build System for Dynamic Infrastructure, was just &lt;a href=&quot;https://yahooeng.tumblr.com/post/155765242061/open-sourcing-screwdriver-yahoos-continuous&quot;&gt;released&lt;/a&gt; with all product &lt;a href=&quot;http://docs.screwdriver.cd&quot;&gt;docs available in English and Japanese&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This community-driven tool will simplify deployment pipelines, optimize for trunk development, and make rolling back easier. Screwdriver handles over 25,000+ builds per day and 12,000+ daily git commits as a single shared entrypoint for Yahoo. It supports multiple languages and handles both virtual machine and container-based builds and deployment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/screwdriver.png&quot; alt=&quot;Screwdriver UI&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Yahoo has been filling the headlines with drastic strategic decisions lately, we are very proud to support Yahoo’s open-source project and take the collaborative results to new places in the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks to a supportive community and its collaborative translation integrated with Locki, Screwdriver docs are now available to developers in 2 languages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/screwdriver_locki.png&quot; alt=&quot;Screwdriver Locki Screenshot&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;we-wish-screwdrivercd-continuous-success-with-continuous-and-additional-language-support&quot;&gt;We wish Screwdriver.cd continuous success, with continuous and additional language support!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More information about the Screwdriver project can be found on the &lt;a href=&quot;http://screwdriver.cd&quot;&gt;official website&lt;/a&gt;, within their &lt;a href=&quot;https://yahooeng.tumblr.com/post/155765242061/open-sourcing-screwdriver-yahoos-continuous&quot;&gt;newest blog post&lt;/a&gt;, or under the &lt;a href=&quot;http://sdtimes.com/yahoo-open-sources-continuous-delivery-tool-screwdriver/&quot;&gt;SD Times news&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Do not forget to chek out the &lt;a href=&quot;http://docs.screwdriver.cd&quot;&gt;bilingual docs in English and Japanese&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://locki.io&quot;&gt;integrate Locki for your (open-source) projects&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
